Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 1984 (Box 2-4)
  - Mugmuk v. Klein 1984 October 05 (Box 3)
  - Muhammad v. Fauver 1984 February 09 (Box 3)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from Nancy B. Stiles; Letter (untitled); Order
    Health facilities and institutions
    Prescription drugs
    Health personnel
  - N.Y. Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear v. Penny Fashions 1984 January 06 (Box 3)
    Wages and earnings
    Labor standards
  - Pizzo v. Cosella 1984 June 12 (Box 3)
  - Ragins v. Super. Ct. 1984 February 01 (Box 3)
    Letter-Opinion; Order of Dismissal; Letter-Opinion for Hunt v. Mercer County Superior Court, et al. (1983 December 08); Opinion of 3rd Cir. for United States, ex rel. Rines v. Beister, et al. (1982 April 29)
  - Rago v. Breining 1984 October 30 (Box 3)
  - Raleigh v. Rockwell Int'l Corp. 1984 January 24 (Box 3)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Order for Leave to File an Amended Answer
  - Rasheed v. Cannon 1984 May 30 (Box 3)
    Opinion; Order of Dismissal
  - Raynor v. United States 1984 October 29 (Box 3)
    Opinion; Order; Letter (untitled); Letter from Rosemary Peters
    Department of Housing and Urban Development
    Housing and community development funding
    Housing finance and home ownership
    Residential rehabilitation and home repair
    Raynor v. United States, 604 F. Supp. 205 (D. N.J. 1984).
  - Raywood v. Mercer County Bd. of Freeholders 1984 May 15 (Box 3)
  - Remington Rand Corp. v. Marine Midland Bank 1984 January 27 (Box 3)
    Bank accounts, deposits, capital
  - Rothschild v. Rothschild 1984 July 19 (Box 3)
    Crimes against children
    Family relationships
    Separation, divorce, custody, support
  - Ryans v. N.J. Comm'n for the Blind & Visually Impaired 1984 August 31 (Box 3)
  - Ryans v. Soc. Sec. Admin. 1984 May 04 (Box 3)
    Social Security Administration
    Department of Veterans Affairs
    Department of Defense
  - Saccenti v. Int'l Business Machines Corp. 1984 July 12 (Box 3)
    Cancer
    Environmental health
    Water quality
    Water use and supply
    Pollution liability
    Hazardous wastes and toxic substances
    Saccenti v. Int'l Business Machines Corp., No. 83-4252, 1984 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 14991 (D. N.J. July 12, 1984).
  - Segnit v. Nat'l R.R. Passenger Corp. 1984 January 27 (Box 3)
  - Simcha Kosher Caterers v. Ins. Co. of N. America 1984 March 28 (Box 3)
  - Simmons v. Tard 1984 January 27 (Box 3)
  - Slater v. Hannay 1984 June 06 (Box 3)
  - Smith v. Amerada Hess Corp. 1984 April 05 (Box 3)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from John E. Flynn
    Motor fuels
  - Soto v. Lee Filters, Inc. 1984 February 01 (Box 3)
  - Stoklasek v. HAD Realty 1984 September 27 (Box 3)
    Letter; Order; Order of Dismissal; Exhibits A, A1, A2, B; Complaint
    Housing industry and standards
  - Terrell v. Tard 1984 February 09 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Order
  - Tucker v. Fauver 1984 March 12 (Box 4)
  - Tucker v. Tard 1984 September 07 (Box 4)
  - Uhrin v. Maldonado 1984 February 01 (Box 4)
  - United States v. Artishenko 1984 June 08 (Box 4)
    Citizenship and naturalization
    Human rights
    War crimes, genocide, crimes against humanity
    Conflicts and wars
    Germany
  - United States v. Cuthbertson 1984 June 29 (Box 4)
    Opinion upon Hearing Pursuant to 28 U.S.C. § 2255; Order; Letter from Sally Mrvos; Judgement Order of 3rd Cir. On appeal (1985 June 26)
  - United States v. Escarda 1984 June 18 (Box 4)
  - United States v. Garcia 1984 June 18 (Box 4)
  - United States v. Morton-Thiokol Corp. 1984 November 15 (Box 4)
    Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)
    Environmental regulatory procedures
  - United States v. Silva 1984 March 01 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibit A; Order Amending Presentence Report
- Papers, 1985 (Box 4-6)
  All papers dated 1985.
  - Allen v. Alfacell Corp. 1985 September 13 (Box 4)
  - Altamura v. News World Commc'n 1985 October 04 (Box 4)
    News media and reporting
    Foreign language
  - Am. Centennial Ins. Co. v. Underwriters, Inc. 1985 November 14 (Box 4)
  - Am. Equip. Leasing Co. v. Tecchio 1985 February 12 (Box 4)
    Computers and information technology
    Pennsylvania
  - Baron v. McClure 1985 September 18 (Box 4)
    Opinion; Order of Dismissal; Order
  - Battle v. County of Union 1985 August 22 (Box 4)
  - Bennett v. Wiechnik 1985 August 22 (Box 4)
    Opinion (x2); Order; Order
  - Bertram Music Co. v. Park Vending 1985 February 04 (Box 4)
    Music
    Performing arts
  - Blohm v. Giordano 1985 March 15 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Letter-Opinion (1985 May 07); Order
  - Blohm v. Springfield Twp. Mun. Ct. 1985 May 07 (Box 4)
  - Blohm v. West Windsor Twp. 1985 May 14 (Box 4)
    Noise pollution
    Environmental assessment, monitoring, research
  - Boinides v. El Diario La Prensa 1985 July 03 (Box 4)
    Opinion; Affidavit of James Geehan; Order
  - Brown v. Foley 1985 June 20 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Opinion of 3rd Cir. On appeal (1987 January 26)
  - Butler Mfg. Co. v. Kuhn & Jacob Molding & Tool Co. 1985 December 19 (Box 4)
    Product safety and quality
    Electric power generation and transmission
  - Caldwell v. Mobil Chem. Co. 1985 April 29 (Box 4)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from West Publishing Co. (with reply message from J. Bissell)
  - Callaway v. Callaway 1985 September 12 (Box 4)
    Massachusetts
  - Cameron v. Corr. Inst. for Women 1985 February 01 (Box 4)
  - Carretta Trucking v. Underwriters at Lloyd's of London 1985 December 09 (Box 4)
    Transcript of Proceedings
  - Cerwinski v. U.S. Dep't of Agric. 1985 May 07 (Box 4)
  - Christopher v. Keister 1985 November 13 (Box 4)
  - Claiborne v. Heckler 1985 August 15 (Box 4)
  - Clauso v. Tard 1985 June 20 (Box 4)
    Letter (untitled); Order
    Health care coverage and access
  - Compolattaro v. O'Lone 1985 June 18 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Report and Recommendation
  - Condone v. Reagan 1985 March 27 (Box 4)
  - Cruz v. Marine Transp. Lines 1985 March 27 (Box 4)
    Opinion (x2); Order (x2)
  - Cutler v. Morris 1985 January 21 (Box 4)
    Letter-Opinion; Report and Recommendation; Order
    Trusts and estates
  - Davis v. Neubert 1985 October 16 (Box 4)
  - Donaghy v. Roudebush 1985 February 19 (Box 4)
    Opinion; Hand-revised Opinion; Two Letters from West Publishing Co.; Letter to West Publishing Co.; Revised Opinion for Publication
    Donaghy v. Roudebush, 614 F. Supp. 585 (D. N.J. 1985).
  - Doron v. F.W. Woolworth Co. 1985 May 13 (Box 4)
  - Dunmore v. Manning 1985 May 31 (Box 4)
  - Fasick v. Hilton 1985 February 05 (Box 4)
  - In re Feldman 1985 December 04 (Box 5)
    Bankruptcy
    Specialized courts
  - G. & J.K. Enter. v. City of South Amboy 1985 February 01 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1985 December 16); Order
    Licensing and registrations
  - Gamble v. City of Toms River 1985 April 04 (Box 5)
    Sex offenses
    Violent crime
  - Hardgove v. Fauver 1985 June 21 (Box 5)
    Memo to Edna; Letter-Opinion; Order
  - Harper v. Fauver 1985 March 21 (Box 5)
  - Hayes v. Kean 1985 October 10 (Box 5)
  - Huertas v. Marine Transp. Lines 1985 November 20 (Box 5)
    California
  - Jabbar v. O'Lone 1985 September 11 (Box 5)
  - Jenin v. Scheidemantel 1985 June 17 (Box 5)
    Letter-Opinion; Report and Recommendation of U.S.M. John W. Devine; Order
  - Jersey Paving Co. v. Fidelity & Deposit Co. 1985 March 01 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order Vacating Order of Consolidation; Order of Remand; Order of Remand; Order of Remand; Order; Erratum Order; Two Letters from James P. Corson; Letter to James P. Corson
    Jersey Paving Co. v. Fidelity & Deposit Co., 603 F. Supp. 414 (D. N.J. 1985).
  - Lentz v. Mac Tools 1985 September 10 (Box 5)
  - Lidman v. Smith 1985 November 21 (Box 5)
  - Lukas v. Nat'l Benefit Life Ins. Co. 1985 January 17 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order Granting Defendant's Motion to Dismiss Plaintiff's Claims for Punitive Damages and Emotional Distress and Denying Plaintiff's Motion to Amend the Complaint
  - Lynch v. W. Johnson 1985 April 15 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order; Letter-Opinion (1985 June 14); Order; Opinion (1985 November 26); Order
    Taxation
  - Malone v. Ford Motor Co. 1985 January 21 (Box 5)
  - Master Diamond Wholesalers Corp. v. Santana 1985 January 16 (Box 5)
    Consumer credit
  - McBride v. Sperber 1985 November 19 (Box 5)
  - McIsaac v. Kanematsu-Gosho, Inc. 1985 November 29 (Box 5)
    Opinion of the 3rd Cir. on appeal; Judgment
    Federal district courts
  - Monroe v. Beyers 1985 June 20 (Box 5)
  - Muhammad v. Fauver 1985 March 21 (Box 5)
  - Napier v. Philips 1985 September 11 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Opinion (1985 September 17); Order
  - Nataraj v. United States 1985 November 15 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Exhibits I, II; Order
    Personnel records
    Temporary and part-time employment
  - Olitsky v. Rafferty 1985 August 22 (Box 5)
  - Paranee v. Twel 1985 March 06 (Box 5)
    Child safety and welfare
  - Pasqua v. Essex County 1985 June 14 (Box 5)
  - Rockwell Int'l v. Midland Transp. Co. 1985 September 24 (Box 5)
    Letter-Opinion; Letter to Robert G. Mazeau; Exhibit G; Order; Order
    Aviation and airports
  - Rodriguez v. Nat'l Eng'g Co. 1985 September 16 (Box 5)
  - Roehsler v. Karcher 1985 January 23 (Box 5)
    Animal protection and human-animal relationships
    Mammals
  - Rothschild v. Rothschild 1985 March 12 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order; Order; Order; Letter-Opinion (1985 May 13); Order
  - Say v. Smith 1985 December 20 (Box 5)
  - Shakoor v. Fauver 1985 December 12 (Box 5)
  - Shane v. Tard 1985 October 31 (Box 5)
    North Carolina
  - Simmons v. Tard 1985 November 27 (Box 5)
  - Stover v. Jersey Cent. Power & Light Co. 1985 March 01 (Box 5)
    Public utilities and utility rates
  - Swangler v. Tard 1985 August 22 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from Charles E. Swangler; Letter to Charles E. Swangler
  - United States v. Caballero 1985 September 24 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Order Denying Relief Pursuant to Motion under 28 U.S.C. § 2255
  - United States v. DeLuca 1985 March 18 (Box 5)
  - United States v. Ewing 1985 May 28 (Box 5)
  - United States v. Lindsley 1985 July 05 (Box 5)
    Opinion; Exhibits A, B, C
  - United States v. Sardina 1985 October 17 (Box 5)
  - United States v. Serpone 1985 June 17 (Box 5)
    Letter-Opinion; Order Denying Motion for Reconsideration
  - United States v. Ten Slot Machines 1985 November 19 (Box 6)
    Gambling
    Hawaii
  - Wells v. Consol. Rail Corp. 1985 January 21 (Box 6)
    Railroads
  - White v. Van Lieu 1985 February 05 (Box 6)
  - Whitted v. Zelinski 1985 March 12 (Box 6)
    Opinion; Order; Notice of Allocation and Assignment; Order of Dismissal
  - Wyckoff v. Wyckoff 1985 December 04 (Box 6)
    Marriage and family status
- Papers, 1986 (Box 6-9)
  All papers dated 1986.
  - Alston v. Fauver 1986 December 01 (Box 6)
  - Anastasio v. Schering Corp. 1986 September 25 (Box 6)
  - Asken v. Quinn 1986 November 10 (Box 6)
  - Bellino v. Kinney 1986 September 15 (Box 6)
    Accounting and auditing
  - Billups v. Wesley-Jessen, Inc. 1986 September 22 (Box 6)
    Age discrimination
  - Blackston v. United States 1986 February 18 (Box 6)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Opinion on Application by Plaintiff-Appellant for Transcripts without Charge; Order (1985 December 12) | Opinion; Order (1985 October 24)
  - Bd. of Ed. of the E. Windsor Reg'l Sch. Dist. v. Diamond 1986 October 17 (Box 6)
    Child care and development
    Educational facilities and institutions
    Special education
  - Bonney v. Hertz Sys. 1986 January 31 (Box 6)
  - Bowes v. Dep't of the Navy 1986 January 24 (Box 6)
  - Brevel Motors v. Vendo Co. 1986 November 03 (Box 6)
    Brevel Motors v. Vendo Co., No. 84-3423, 1986 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18277 (D. N.J. Oct. 31, 1986).
  - Brown v. Dietz 1986 July 29 (Box 6)
  - Cardozo v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1986 September 29 (Box 6)
  - Coleman v. Becton Dickinson & Co. 1986 September 19 (Box 6)
  - Condone v. Sec'y of the Army 1986 June 25 (Box 6)
  - Conn. Gen. Life Ins. Co. v. E. Dental Ctr. of Ewing 1986 March 03 (Box 6)
    Order; Order | Letter-Opinion; Order (1986 May 08) | Opinion; Order (1986 November 12)
  - In re Corvelli 1986 December 03 (Box 6)
  - Cox v. Hilton 1986 December 16 (Box 6)
  - Cummis v. RRI XX Mgmt. Corp. 1986 July 24 (Box 6)
  - Curry v. Tard 1986 July 08 (Box 6)
    Opinion; Order; Memo from Michael Jankoski (1986 September 04); Letter from Lyle P. Hough (1986 August 28); Letter to Lyle P. Hough (1986 August 18); Letter to Rudolph J. Curry (1986 February 19); Letter from Rudolph J. Curry (1986 July 20); Letter to Rudolph J. Curry (1986 November 18); Letter to Philip J. Moran (nd)
  - Drayton v. Fauver 1986 September 24 (Box 6)
  - Dressler v. Plantier 1986 March 17 (Box 6)
    Opinion; Stipulation of Dismissal; Order; Order
  - East Wind Indus. v. U.S. Dep't of the Treasury 1986 June 18 (Box 6)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Robert E. Cowen)
  - Ekins v. Kenworth Truck Co. 1986 October 16 (Box 6)
  - Falter v. Veterans Admin. 1986 January 31 (Box 6)
    Opinion (x2); Order (x2); Letter to William F. Culleton and Anne C. Singer (1986 April 16) (x2); Errata Order (1986 April 17); Letter from Anne C. Singer (1986 February 13); Letter from Anne C. Singer (1986 March 26); Letter to Thomas P. Adler (1986 May 19); Letter from Thomas P. Adler (1986 May 13)
    Hospital care
    Medical ethics
    Nursing
  - Farese v. Hicks 1986 January 09 (Box 6)
    Digestive and metabolic diseases
  - Federal Inv. Corp. v. Reid 1986 September 22 (Box 6)
    Opinion; Order Dismissing Appeal
  - Freund v. Heckler 1986 September 29 (Box 6)
  - Garolis v. Tr. of the Trucking Employees of N. Jersey Welfare Fund 1986 June 16 (Box 6)
  - Gendzwill v. Ziff-Davis Publ'g Co. 1986 February 28 (Box 6)
    Transcript of Proceedings; Order
    Unemployment
  - Gen. Accident Ins. Co. v. Torres 1986 October 31 (Box 6)
    Insurance industry and regulation
  - Gilmore v. State 1986 September 24 (Box 6)
  - Gonzalez v. Two or More Named Unknown U.S. Customs Serv. Employees 1986 March 24 (Box 6)
    Smuggling and trafficking
    Border security and unlawful immigration
    Argentina
  - Grant v. Ewing 1986 February 10 (Box 7)
  - Grant v. Vitanzo 1986 February 10 (Box 7)
  - Gruen Indus. v. Gruen Elec. 1986 October 16 (Box 7)
    Opinion; Order; Report and Recommendation of U.S.M. Serena Perretti (1985 September 30)
  - Haag v. Fauver 1986 June 18 (Box 7)
  - Harris v. Eisenberg, Honig & Fogler 1986 November 05 (Box 7)
  - Helbig v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. 1986 June 12 (Box 7)
  - Horowitz Fin. Corp. v. Wolf Creek Vill., Inc. 1986 November 19 (Box 7)
    Cooperative and condominium housing
    Utah
  - Improta v. Weehawken Bd. of Ed. 1986 April 22 (Box 7)
    Teaching, teachers, curricula
  - Int'l Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Local 220 v. Solomon 1986 July 31 (Box 7)
  - J. I. Hass Co. v. Gilbane Bldg. Co. 1986 October 07 (Box 7)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order Quashing Subpoenas (1986 December 15)
    Business records
  - Johnson v. Gregorio 1986 July 22 (Box 7)
  - Johnson v. Monmouth County Bd. of Chosen Freeholders 1986 April 30 (Box 7)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from Richard A. Amadur (1986 May 01); Letter from Michael Johnson (1986 May 07); Letter from Michael Johnson (1986 May 13); Letter to Michael Johnson (1986 May 20)
  - Jolley v. Tard 1986 April 04 (Box 7)
  - Jones v. Jersey Cent. Power & Light Co. 1986 January 15 (Box 7)
  - Jones v. Smith 1986 May 06 (Box 7)
  - Kicklighter v. United States 1986 March 18 (Box 7)
    Defense spending
  - Kilbarr Corp. v. Amsterdam-Rotterdam Bank 1986 October 31 (Box 7)
    Opinion | Letter to Bruce E. Clark and James C. McConnon; Order (1986 December 30)
    Netherlands
  - Kilbarr Corp. v. Business Sys., Inc. 1986 September 24 (Box 7)
    Opinion; Order; Letter from Louis J. Virelli (1986 October 14) | Opinion; Judgment (1986 June 27); Brief in Support of Motion to Correct Judgment under Rule 60(a) (1986 July 14); Order Correcting Judgment under Rule 60(a) (1986 August 06); Order Amending Opinion (1986 August 07)
    Trade secrets and economic espionage
  - Kurash v. Mountain Leisure Assoc. 1986 March 05 (Box 7)
    Outdoor recreation
  - La Marca v. Travelers Ins. Co. 1986 October 28 (Box 7)
    Interest, dividends, interest rates
  - Laifer v. Twin County Grocers 1986 June 26 (Box 7)
  - Lake v. United States 1986 September 18 (Box 7)
  - Lord v. Tard 1986 June 19 (Box 7)
    Order
    [file missing]
  - Martino v. Metro. Transit Auth. 1986 June 20 (Box 7)
    Vocational education
  - McGill v. Schiedemantel 1986 March 07 (Box 7)
  - McGilloway v. Berkshire Life Ins. Co. 1986 June 13 (Box 7)
  - McIsaac v. Kanematsu-Gosho, Inc. 1986 June 12 (Box 7)
    Letter-Opinion; Order for De Bene Esse Depositions in Japan | Opinion; Order (1986 July 10)
    Japan
  - McNamara v. Brown 1986 April 18 (Box 7)
  - In re Menon 1986 February 19 (Box 7)
  - Mentzel v. Fountain Motel 1986 February 06 (Box 7)
  - Mentzel v. Hollmann 1986 March 11 (Box 7)
    Transcript of Proceedings | Transcript of Proceedings (1986 June 11)
    Wisconsin
  - Miller v. Honda Motor Co. 1986 December 10 (Box 7)
    Opinion (incomplete); Order
    Bermuda
  - Mirault v. Neubert 1986 June 30 (Box 7)
    Opinion; Order of Dismissals; Order
  - Mokone v. Maaga 1986 May 01 (Box 7)
  - Molas v. Marine Eng'r Beneficial Ass'n Pension Trust 1986 October 23 (Box 7)
  - Molese v. Bergen County Prosecutor's Office 1986 July 31 (Box 7)
  - Murphy v. Gen. Elec. Credit Corp. 1986 August 01 (Box 7)
  - Narvaez v. Rodriguez 1986 November 05 (Box 8)
  - Nasmith v. City of Newark 1986 November 03 (Box 8)
    Hate crimes
  - Nat'l Amateur Roller Skating Ass'n v. U.S. Amateur Confederation of Roller Skating 1986 September 19 (Box 8)
    Athletes
  - National Indus. Group Pension Plan v. Gluntz Brass & Aluminum Foundry Co. 1986 September 24 (Box 8)
  - Newspaper Guild of N.Y. v. Middlesex County Publ'g Co. 1986 March 03 (Box 8)
  - Nina Ricci v. FAP Imports, Inc. 1986 November 07 (Box 8)
    Motion for Preliminary Injunction - Argument (Draft from "MQ")
  - Nyberg v. Wood Indus. 1986 October 15 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Report and Recommendation of U.S.M. G. Donald Haneke; Order of Dismissal
  - Oliver v. Prisciotta 1986 July 24 (Box 8)
  - Oppenheim v. Hartford Ins. Group 1986 December 17 (Box 8)
    Connecticut
    New York State
  - Panzitta v. United States 1986 August 14 (Box 8)
    Order | Opinion; Order (1985 December 04)
  - Penna v. Rafferty 1986 June 25 (Box 8)
  - Progressive Inv. Corp. v. Midland Ins. Co. 1986 May 28 (Box 8)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1986 July 01)
  - Quantum Prod. Serv. v. Pub. Serv. Elec. & Gas Co. 1986 July 01 (Box 8)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1986 October 16) | Opinion (1986 December 03)
    Oil and gas
    Alternative and renewable resources
    Energy revenues and royalties
    General energy matters
    Energy storage, supplies, demand
    Solid waste and recycling
  - Ramco Am. Int'l v. Air Operations Int'l 1986 April 11 (Box 8)
    Opinion; Order Dismissing Complaint
  - Robinson v. Edwards 1986 July 09 (Box 8)
  - Rothschild v. Rothschild 1986 June 03 (Box 8)
  - Schlobohm v. Wagner 1986 June 03 (Box 8)
  - Schwec v. United States 1986 April 29 (Box 8)
  - Shible v. United States 1986 February 13 (Box 8)
    Opinion; Order | Letter from West Publishing Co. (with reply message from J. Bissell); Two pages from Vol. 57, American Federal Tax Reports, 2nd Series; Letter from Frederick T. Day | Letter-Opinion; Order (1986 April 15) | Order (1986 August 13)
  - Shihadeh v. Tard 1986 January 09 (Box 8)
  - Sigler v. D'Amico 1986 June 24 (Box 8)
  - Smith v. Rafferty 1986 March 05 (Box 8)
  - State v. Thomas 1986 December 16 (Box 8)
    Public Lands and Natural Resources
    Department of the Interior
  - Supka v. Worldwide Yacht Charters 1986 February 18 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Judgment Order
    Consumer affairs
  - Taylor v. Wyeth Lab. 1986 April 09 (Box 8)
    Opinion; Order; Errata Order
    Child health
    Drug safety, medical device, and laboratory regulation
    Health technology, devices, supplies
    Immunology
  - Terrell v. Tard 1986 May 16 (Box 8)
  - Tiger Inn v. Edwards 1986 June 09 (Box 8)
    Higher education
    Women's education
  - Tilley v. Schering Corp. 1986 December 03 (Box 8)
  - Twp. of Clinton v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1986 June 18 (Box 8)
    Opinion (opinion of Chief Judge Fisher)
    Small towns
  - Twp. of Ocean v. Int'l Surplus Lines Ins. Co. 1986 June 09 (Box 8)
  - Trombetta v. Peil 1986 July 22 (Box 8)
  - United States v. Escarda 1986 December 29 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibits A, B; Order
  - United States v. Febre 1986 June 18 (Box 8)
    Opinion Denying Motion under 28 U.S.C. § 2255; Order Denying Relief Pursuant to Motion under 28 U.S.C. § 2255
  - United States v. Gallagher 1986 June 12 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Letter-Opinion; Order (1986 October 07) | Letter-Opinion; Order (1986 December 16)
    Arizona
  - United States v. Gambino 1986 November 12 (Box 8)
  - United States v. Liberto 1986 December 31 (Box 8)
  - United States v. Lindsley 1986 June 23 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibits A, B, C; Order
    Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
    Government ethics and transparency, public corruption
    Government information and archives
  - United States v. Ten Slot Machines 1986 August 12 (Box 8)
  - United States v. Thomas 1986 April 29 (Box 8)
    Letter-Opinion; Order; Letter from Eric Thomas
  - Varca v. Fauver 1986 June 03 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Order; Order | Letter-Opinion; Order
  - Vornado v. Tr. of the Retail Store Employees' Union, Local 1262 1986 December 03 (Box 9)
  - Washington v. Hilton 1986 March 17 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Report and Recommendation of U.S.M. John W. Devine; Order for Judgment
  - Weiss v. United States 1986 November 12 (Box 9)
  - White v. Van Lieu 1986 April 18 (Box 9)
  - Williams v. Collier 1986 March 10 (Box 9)
  - Young Life v. Young Life of Africa 1986 March 21 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Order for Partial Summary Judgment Granting Permanent Injunction
    Social work, volunteer service, charitable organizations
  - Zamboni v. Stamler 1986 May 09 (Box 9)
- Papers, 1987 (Box 9-13)
  All papers dated 1987.
  - Abate v. Monroe Sys. for Bus. 1987 June 30 (Box 9)
  - Admin. Office of the U.S. Courts 1987 December 18 (Box 9)
    Memorandum: "H.R. 3483 - The Criminal Fines Improvement Act of 1987 (P.L. 100-185); S 1822 - The Sentencing Act of 1987 (P.L. 100-182)"
  - Am. Centennial Ins. v. Underwriters, Inc. 1987 September 23 (Box 9)
  - Anastasio v. Schering Corp. 1987 February 18 (Box 9)
    Letter-Opinion; Order Denying Defendant's Motion for a New Trial and Awarding Plaintiff Supplemental Attorneys Fees and Costs
  - Anthony Petroleum v. Baii Banking Corp. 1987 June 22 (Box 9)
    White-collar crime
  - Artway v. Scheidemantel 1987 October 28 (Box 9)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Robert E. Cowen); Order
    Constitution and constitutional amendments
  - Asken v. Thomas 1987 February 09 (Box 9)
  - Axelrod v. U.S. Judiciary 1987 May 26 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Dismissal Order
  - Baldwin v. Bonazzi 1987 December 22 (Box 9)
  - Barbosa v. Harris 1987 February 13 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Order; Order for Judgment (1987 May 12)
    Crime victims
    Parks, recreation areas, trails
  - Barry v. Brower 1987 August 14 (Box 9)
  - Battle v. County of Union 1987 September 30 (Box 9)
  - Bench Comment (Publication of the Federal Judicial Center) 1987 December 01 (Box 9)
    Newsletter 1987 No. 5: "Postindictment restraining orders under the Comprehensive Forfeiture Act"
  - Blanks v. Heckler 1987 July 10 (Box 9)
  - In re Bob's E. Contracting 1987 January 15 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Exhibits A, B; Order
  - Brown v. Grabowski 1987 September 30 (Box 9)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1987 September 30)
    Domestic violence and child abuse
    Crimes against women